Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Until someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you want to be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
Now, which one of you is Arlong?
Well, that just happens to be my name.
You can call me Luffy.
Luffy, what are you
supposed to be? A pirate.
Hold it right there.
Where do you think you're going?
You want to talk to the boss?
Well, you got to talk to us first, get it?
So let's talk.
That's far enough.
Move it!
So, what does a pirate want with me?
Who the hell are you?
Luffy, help me.
That's making our navigator cry!
Back off, you're out of your league.
Jeez, you just had to
run on ahead by yourself.
Don't worry, I can handle
these bozos on my own.
Aw, you fool.
I never said anything about being worried.
I just don't want you
hogging all the action. Oh.
Well, I just want to let you guys know
that I don't mind if you hog at all.
I see you're raring to go, as usual.
It's him!
That's the unknown swordsman
I was telling you about!
Roa Noah Zoro. I thought so.
That bastard tricked me.
I can't believe it.
I fell for it.
Look, Sian and Yanker.
Wait, hook, lion, and sinker.
Hey, look, long nose.
But he's dead!
We saw Nami kill him!
But Nami was a traitor all along.
Just as I suspected.
Who are those guys?
Hold it!
That guy just decked Arlong.
Unbelievable!
No human should be able to do that.
Are they?
Didn't we tell you?
Just stay back here Now do you understand
why we're keeping you
away from that fight?
You guys will just get
in their way But why?
That's what I don't understand What
reason could they possibly have to fight?
Reason?
Big Sis Nami was crying
Do they need any more reason than
that to put their lives on the line?
A pirate, of course.
This is all starting to make sense now!
You've been after Nami
this whole time. But.
The girl is mine and
I'm not giving her up!
A bunch of idiots like you
aren't worth Arlong's time!
We know how to deal with you!
Not that.
Oh, no, it's here!
What is going on here, guys?
Mama, rise!
It's a monster!
That's the beast from the Grand Line
that destroyed the town of Gosa!
It's actually real! Oh no!
It's Momo!
Well, look who's back.
Seems he's a friend of the fishmen.
Hey, stop!
Where are you going?
Get back here, Mama!
You can't just leave! Mama!
Leaving?
Now, now, isn't that a shame?
But, I suppose if you really want to
run away, Then who am I to stop you?
Well then...
It's coming right before us!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
You're all mine, you dumb cow.
Looks like he's got a
plan for once. We'll see.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
His arm's drenched!
So he must have devil
fruit powers. Powers?
Aw, who cares?
Attack!
Hey, let's get out of here.
Whoa, wait.
What's he gonna do?
I'm not sure if I want to find out.
Time for something new!
Gum-Gum!
IT WILL!
Alright, that's it, Arlong!
I'm done playing games with you!
I didn't come here to beat
down all your cronies!
I came here to teach you a lesson!
So step up!
Oh, I will. Don't worry.
Actually, I was just thinking about
how painfully I'll end your life.
That was the worst plan ever!
Yeah, well, you're trying
to kill all of us, too!
That boy's incredible.
I just can't believe there's a human
who can throw that giant monster!
It's as if the gods
themselves are fighting.
How dare you hurt our brother?
Very well, it seems that we
must now join in the fight!
Now you'll get an education in
the inferiority of your species!
Oh really, I'd like to see that!
Relax, sir!
Let us handle this!
If you go on one of your
rampages to squash these insects,
you destroy all of Arlong Park. Choo!
Please, just let us kill these weaklings!
All right, they're yours.
Uh, guys, there's something
I should tell you.
What the hell's that octopus doing?
Octopus is best when
it's cut thin and salted.
Add some olive oil and paprika and it
makes the perfect snack while drinking.
So listen to me, guys,
I'm kind of in trouble.
Take this!
Zero vision!
Hachi Inchie!
Idiot!
How come you didn't dodge that?
I can't see Squat!
Now to finish you off!
Come on, get out of there, Loopy, run!
Yeah, that's the problem.
I can't run.
I can't even walk.
My feet are kind of stuck.
But you're the one who stuck them
into the ground in the first place!
Always thinking ahead.
One Hachi inkjet served on the rocks!
You're such a pain.
Sanji, that was so
totally awesomely awesome!
Looks like I ended up picking one
hell of an idiot to be my captain.
We all did.
Luffy's great! Hey!
But the truth is that our idiot captain is
far better than a gang
who'd prey on a lady.
A lady, huh?
Huh?
You rushed into certain
death for one lousy girl?
Lousy girl?
If you insult Nami one more time,
I can promise that you'll go
from fish man to fish sticks.
Got that?
Your skills are quite
exceptional for a human,
but I must admit that chivalry from
a pirate seems just a little fake.
I'm damn good at what I do.
And I guarantee you there's nothing fake.
About my desire to help
a beautiful lady in need.
Looks like I'll be acquainting you.
With the true superiority
of the fishman's species.
Nice work, but they're still stuck. Still?
They're still stuck?
We could pull all day And I bet my
legs would still be stuck in there.
Hey, are you trying at all?
Or do you want to stay stuck here?
Maybe no one told you that the penalty for
playing around in Arlong Park was just...
Come on, get unstuck already, get unstuck!
Please, Luffy, come on!
Come here!
Hey, Octopus.
They're a little bit busy at the moment.
Why don't you take me on?
Oooh, you're Zoro!
I forgot!
You can't get away with tricking me!
And how dare you mercilessly
slaughter so many of my brothers!
That stuff's old news, Octopus Man.
I personally don't care what reasons
you have for wanting to kill me.
The situation has changed.
You see, the tables have turned.
You're not the hunters
anymore, understand?
Now it's you fish freaks
who are being hunted
tell him Zoro that octopus guy is yours
Hey, I'm back.
Oh You're dead I get it now.
You must actually want me to kill you
Hold on.
Wasn't that the guy who
saved Genzo's life earlier?
Hey, wait.
You're the people from Cocoyashi.
Judging from the fact
that you all have weapons,
I can only assume that
this is a rebellion.
Then you'll all have to...
Exploding stars!
Get through Usa!
Did you think it would be easy?
You're dealing with me now!
Enough!
I'm going to get rid of you right now.
Who is that lad?
Brave one minute and cowardly the next.
He's a baffling man.
Get back here, Long Nose!
Oh, you're one to talk, Big Mouth!
Why are these people pirates?
You morons are a pathetic sight to behold.
I'm sick of watching this now.
Get out of my way!
But sir, there's no
reason to go on a rampage.
Think of our long park.
Don't worry. I won't.
I just thought of a fun game that's all.
Now you're going down!
Do you honestly think your sad
little group can defeat us?
So what if we do?
Yeah, so what if we do, huh?
Now let go!
You got something to say to us?
Did you know that those with
Devil Fruit powers can't swim?
But honestly, anybody in this situation
would sink right to the bottom!
Gum-Gum Pistol! The sea! No!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
OUCHI!
You fool!
How pointless.
Luffy!
Damn you!
Wait don't be stupid those fishmen can't
wait for us to jump in the water after him.
They'd have an obvious advantage
in an underwater fight.
There's only one way to
save Luffy we've got to
take these guys out at
the same time then go in.
Water there's no time come on let's do it.
Yeah so how long can he
hold out time? Is ticking.
Oh so that's the game
I get it you can take
the fish you slice and trim the octopus.
This is bad.
I'm almost out of breath.
What now?
He can't help himself.
What do we do?
Big Bro Luffy's gonna die!
They can't even breathe underwater.
Humans are such pitiful
creatures, aren't they?
Hey, calamari, let's go.
Game, game!
I'll kick your ass in five seconds flat.
We don't have more than three.
Hey, what's the rush?
You're both running headlong into death.
None of you will leave this place alone.
Oh, crap!
I'm gonna be killed!
I'll beat his ass real quick
and then come save you, Luffy.
A-chi-ing-cha!
No, you bastard! My hair!
But it's okay.
It's only hair.
It'll grow back. Huh?
Now, Zoro, you can't beat me.
I have six hands that will mesmerize
you with their wiggly beauty. Shut up!
Oh, jeez!
Triple! Sword! Catch!
Now, you will see my skills!
That hurt!
I don't have time for this crap.
No, not now.
Is he still hurt?
Lose focus and you lose your luck!
I bet you taste good! Butter!
I've got no time left! No time!
Why don't you die?!
Too bad!
Hunchy suckers are stuck!
Don't just stick there!
Get down here and fight!
Damn coward.
Stupid octopus.
He's just trying to waste our time.
But if we try to save Luffy now,
they'll just drag us to the
bottom of the sea and we'll drown.
If we sit here and do nothing,
then Luffy drowns for sure.
We've got to think of a way to help him.
Yeah. Hold on.
What good are the two of you going to do
in the sea when you both can barely walk?
If you're trying to figure out
a way to save that young man,
Then I believe I should be the
one to volunteer ahead of you!
You'll save him?
Genzo, I'm coming with you.
Let's do it! I'm in.
I'm going alone.
The fishmen will suspect that we're up to
something if we go with
such a large crowd.
And I fear doing so may
cause more harm than good.
But we could help them.
Now another word about it.
There's no point endangering
more people than we have to.
I must go alone.
Yes, thank you.
We're counting on you.
But please, hurry.
Hold on.
Genzo, I'm going too.
No, Gecko, you're hurt.
You're not going to
leave me out of this when
those guys are fighting
for my sister's life.
You can't.
Fine.
Come on, we have to hurry. Right.
I'm sorry.
If only I was stronger.
Please save Luffy.
Don't be too late.
Hey, I have a question that I've
been meaning to ask you, Zoro.
You're famous for your three-sword
technique, so why are you only using one?
You're running scared with one.
Why would I need three?
Shut up!
I've just been playing around with you.
Actually, humans can't defeat me.
I can tell you why, but I think
it'd be more fun to show you.
Yeah, show. I like that.
I think you're really going
to enjoy it a lot, too.
Damn it.
I can't fight back the pain.
Crap, I thought as much.
You still haven't recovered
from your fight with Hawkeye?
Zoro!
Now you may tremble in fear
at Hachi's way of six blades.
Hey, you're not supposed to die yet!
I haven't even killed you.
No! Zoro! I knew it!
He's been faking it!
So true.
The way he's been pummeled would kill any
normal guy, but he tries to fight anyway.
What'd you say?
I thought it was strange.
He walked around just like nothing had
happened after such a horrible fight.
He's laid out flat.
I told you to pay attention
to me, you weakling.
I'm a 40th Don in Fishman Karate.
Whoa, what the...
What the hell just happened?
Sanji?
It can't be him!
Sanji!
They're taking care of, Arlong.
What would you like us to do with Zoro?
What a waste of time.
Just toss him in the sea.
Hardly entertaining.
Aww, that's all?
Well, they did manage
to make a bit of a mess.
No big deal.
As long as Arlong Park
is still standing. True.
No fair!
He killed himself!
I never got the chance to show
him how great of a swordsman I am!
If he could have died on one of my six
blades, I could have stolen his fame!
Well, it's no matter.
There isn't a human alive that can
compare to my way of six blades!
Behold the superior power that only a
six-armed Master Swordsman can attain!
Enough, Hachi.
I understand how you must feel, but if
you continue this little demonstration?
you'll destroy Arlong Park. Oh!
I'm sorry.
I forgot I could destroy stuff.
Don't get carried away.
I'm fine now.
Way of six blades.
What a loser!
Way to go!
You're not dead.
Let me make this clear for you.
You're sorry excuse for a swordsman
There's a certain man.
I have to face and then till I see him
Death himself cannot touch me.
Ah!
He's still alive!
All right, big bro!
That's the best punch that fish man's got.
The old man's kicks were a
hundred times worse than that!
And I never even died.
Stop following me!
I'm alone, but always now
I'm done, I'll keep you near.
As I drift away, I pray you'll
watch me as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise, I begin to wonder?
What could be the reason
it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you.
Show me how to catch those feelings.
Get them to come back to me.
I'll do what I must be.
Because they're everything I want to be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams.
And pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way.